<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Business Plan &amp; Startup Quick Builder</string>


    <string name="thirty_ways" tools:ignore="ExtraTranslation,TypographyEllipsis">
        \n We have written 30 authentic ways to earn from online sources by our experts, find details in app:
        \n\n- Uber or Lyft: If you are in a locale where you can find Uber or Lyft, or one of the many competitors
        around the world such as China…
        \n\n-<b> Postmates:</b> You do not even need a car in some locations to make money with this app...
        \n\n-<b> Swagbucks:</b> With Swagbucks, there are a number of ways you can make money...
        \n\n-<b> Upwork:</b> This website offers a great marketplace for selling just about any professional service...
        \n\n-<b> Fiverr:</b> Based Fivver was started in 2010 by Shal Wininger and Micha Kaufam. You can offer gigs as low as
        $5...
        \n\n-<b> YouTube:</b> Here, we have collected 50 YouTube tutorials that will give you all the basics
        to learn both the fun (like poker or calligraphy) and the practical (like CPR or how to clean a cast
        iron pan). But we are going to share in our next app and will share with you...
        \n\n- <b>Shopify:</b> Want to build your own storefront? You could opt to create a Shopify store. You could also
        install WooCommerce...
        \n\n Learn More Below and Tell us What you Think!
    </string>

    <string name="chat_live">

    What business does not want to increase their sales conversions while decreasing their costs?
    Live chat is a cost efficient way to service your customers; we have already discussed how it
    increases your conversions and average purchase price, but it also allows you to outsource lead
    management at a high volume.
    \n\n

    If you have your website then create live chat option in it. Live Chat helps you greet your
    customers
    pro-actively while they are going through you website
    using the auto greetings function and it also allows them to chat with you anonymously without
    providing their personal details like email or phone. This specifically helps during sales.

        <b>\n\n In the future Updates, we are going to give live chat rooms to you on this website!</b>

    </string>

    <string name="plan_business">

        Every business needs to have a written business plan. Whether it is to provide direction or attract investors, a
        business plan is vital for the success for your organization. But, how do you write a business plan?
        \n\n
        To write the perfect plan, you must know your company, your product, your competition and the market
        intimately.\n\n
        1. Research, research, research.
        \n\n2. Create a company profile.
        \n\n3. Document all aspects of your business.
        \n\n4. Make it adaptable based on your audience.
        \n\n5. Explain why you care.
        Whether you’re sharing your plan with an investor, customer or team member, your plan needs to show that you’re
        passionate and dedicated, and you actually care about your business and the plan. You could discuss the mistakes
        that you have learned, list the problems that you’re hoping to solve, describe your values, and establish what
        makes
        you stand out from the competition.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="execute_business">

        Every year millions of entrepreneurs come up with great ideas. And every year they spend countless hours
        creating
        and re-creating detailed business and strategic plans. Often most of this effort goes to waste as entrepreneurs
        fail
        to follow through on their own well thought-out plans.
        \n\n
        1. Set clear priorities.
        \n\n2. Collect and analyze data.
        \n\n3. Keep a rhythm to meetings.
        \n\n4. Evaluate the strategy.
        \n\n5. None-page strategic plan.
        The entrepreneur should also meet with the executive team and key management personnel on a monthly or quarterly
        basis to evaluate the progress with the strategic plan. These strategic meetings should be more in-depth and
        designed to determine if changes are required.\n\n
        To ensure that the entire organization keeps in sync with the entrepreneurs vision and strategic plan, the
        staff
        should gather periodically for different types of update meetings.\n\n
        The executives should evaluate what is working and continue these proceses and enhance them to boost
        performance.
        With failing results, they should determine what processes do not work and make immediate adjustments to prevent
        further deterioration.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="create_rev">

        <b>Create your revenue:</b>

        Business sell products or services in order to generate revenue. For example, a barber offers a service—a
        haircut—and makes money off of the sale. Business can also generate money through licensing (which can be
        thought of
        as selling their name or their brand as a product), through investments, and other means, but selling products
        and/or services is the most common method. (Quora)\n\n

        Josh Kaufman Explains The ‘4 Methods to Increase Revenue’\n\n

        <b>Believe it or not, there are only four ways to increase your revenue:</b>

        \n\n1. Increase the number of customers.
        \n\n2. Increase the average transaction size.
        \n\n3. Increase the frequency of transactions per customer.
        \n\n4. Raise your prices.

        Increasing the number of customers means you’re trying to bring more people in the door. This strategy is
        relatively
        straightforward: more visitors to your restaurant will equal more tabs, which (assuming the average transaction
        size
        stays the same), will bring in more money.\n\n

        Always focus the majority of your efforts on serving your ideal customers. Your ideal customers buy early, buy
        often, spend the most, spread the word, and are willing to pay a premium for the value you provide.\n\n

        “Money is plentiful for those who understand the simple laws which govern its acquisition.”

        George Clayson, author of The Richest Man in Babylon
    </string>

    <string name="marketing_business">

        <b>Marketing of your business:</b>

        Focus on the uniqueness of your product or service and how the customer will benefit from using the products or
        services you are offering. Use these questions to write a paragraph summarizing these aspects for your marketing
        plan:\n\n

        \n\nWhat are the features of your product or service?
        \n\nDescribe the physical attributes of your product or service, and any other relevant features such as what it
        does or how your product or service differs from competitors products or services.
        \n\nHow will your product or service benefit the customer?
        \n\nRemember that benefits can be intangible as well as tangible; for instance, if you are selling a cleaning
        product,
        your customers will benefit by having a cleaner house, but they may also benefit by enjoying better health.

        \n\n
        Examples of Unique Selling Propositions:
        \n\n

        ·<b> Domino s Pizza</b> - "We deliver hot, fresh pizza in 30 minutes or less, or it is free."
        \n\n

        ·<b> FedEx Corporation</b> - "When it absolutely, positively has to be there overnight."
        \n\n

        ·<b> M Ms</b> - "The milk chocolate melts in your mouth, not in your hand."
        \n\n

        ·<b> Dollar Shave Club</b> - “Everything you need in the bathroom - from razor blades to grooming products -
        automatically
        delivered to your door. It does not get any simpler than that.”
        \n\n

        While small businesses often have minuscule (or non-existent) promotion budgets, that does not mean that small
        businesses cannot design and implement effective promotion plans.
        \n\n
        No business is too small to have a marketing plan. After all, no business is too small for customers or clients.
        And
        if you have these, you need to communicate with them about your products and/or services.
    </string>

    <string name="networking" tools:ignore="TypographyEllipsis">

        <b>NETWORKING</b>
        \n\n
        Networking is a socioeconomic business activity by which businesspeople and entrepreneurs meet to form business
        relationships and to recognize, create, or act upon business opportunities, share information and seek potential
        partners for ventures.\n\n

        In fact, people have been networking as long as they have been communicating with one another. Business
        networking
        simply refers to building and cultivating relationships with people of similar interests in ways that can
        benefit
        all parties. … They might join groups, attend networking events or network in online forums.\n\n
        \n\n
        In this business, your net worth is literally determined by the size of your network.
        \n\n1- Choose Products to Sell. ...
        \n\n2- Gather Networking Tips. ...
        \n\n3- Choose Your Network Marketing Opportunity. ...
        \n\n4- Set Up a Business Phone. ...
        \n\n5- Start a Website. ...
        \n\n6- Create Postcards. ...
        \n\n7- Prepare a Mailing List. ...
        \n\n8- Mail Postcards.
        \n\n
        Why Networking Is Important for Small Business. Small business owners use networking as a means to form
        relationships with others, in like or related fields, that help to expand their business ability to find new
        customers, partner and grow. A key element to effective networking is to make you known.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="think_of_money">

        <b>7 HABITS THAT WILL TRAIN YOUR MIND TO INCREASE YOUR INCOME:\n\n</b>
        1. THE BRAIN NEEDS SOME GRATITUDE PRACTICE!\n\n
        The brain is wired to seek immediate gratification. When it comes to making money and building wealth, immediate
        gratification is the enemy.\n\n

        2. YOU’RE IN CONTROL\n\n
        While our brain may be relatively primitive, this chunk of gray matter still takes its cues from you. As such,
        it is essential to spend some time evaluating your strengths and weaknesses when it comes to wealth
        generation.\n\n

        3. MONEY DOESN’T INSPIRE YOUR BRAIN\n\n
        What are your fundamental needs?\n

        Human beings require four things: food, sex, shelter, and water. These are primary motivators.\n

        Money, meanwhile, is a secondary motivator – and becomes more or less powerful depending on how you use it.\n\n

        4. MONEY MUST MEAN SOMETHING\n\n
        As mentioned, money itself isn’t a motivating force for the brain. However, contextualizing motivations –
        financial security, money management, money values, peace of mind, etc. – helps your brain solidify the abstract
        connection between money and desires.\n\n

        5. YOUR BRAIN MAY NEED A REBOOT\n\n
        You hold conscious and subconscious opinions on everything related to money; including how one makes money, how
        one manages money, how wealthy people “behave,” and how much is “enough,” for example.\n\n

        6. YOUR BRAIN IS CAPABLE OF AMAZING GROWTH\n\n
        We’re all human beings, and it can feel as if it’s nearly impossible to reverse lousy money habits, learn about
        wealth, and so on. But this is just not true.\n\n

        7. REGARDING MONEY, YOUR BRAIN CAN BE A FRIEND OR FOE\n\n
        To wrap things up, it is helpful to understand and remember some basic neuropsychology. You’ll notice as you go
        through this “For You/Against You” list for the brain that the concepts can apply to pretty much ANY endeavor,
        including financial management, success, and freedom.
        \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_create_business_plan">

        <b>
            What is a Business Plan for?
        </b>

        \n\n

        Just because it is the status quo should never be a line in the vocabulary of a startup founder today.
        Traditional business plans can be big beasts of a project that suck time, money and mojo at a vital moment.
        Do not do it unless you know why and what you are trying to achieve with it.

        \n\n
        In fact, you can learn from our business tab now. In short:
        \n\n
        <b>
            What makes a great business plan?
        </b>
        \n\n
        Format, substance, and key data that viewers expect are all important.
        So is the time you spend on it, and when you do it.

        \n\n
        A business plan plays a critical role in launching a profitable and sustainable venture today. New trends
        and the data show us that the best time to complete a robust plan may now come later in the journey than it used
        to. It is much more important to get started, test, and secure funding first.
        \n\n
        <b>In the next update you can create your plans!</b>

    </string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" />

</resources>

